Exercise 1-53, phrasal verb quiz. Mark the proper syllables. One, the plane took off.
The takeoff was worse than the landing. Two, clean up on aisle five. Please clean
up the mess on aisle five. Three, why is he showing off? He's such a show-off.
Four, we need to check in. What time is check-in? Five. We missed the cutoff time
by five minutes. Why did they have to cut it off so early? Six. The kids were
playing dress up. The adults had to dress up for the dinner party. Seven. The
teachers handed out the tests, but missed giving us one of the most important
handouts. Eight. The workers wanted jobs, not handouts. Nine. Wake up. We missed the
wake up call. 10. We had such a nice get-together. We should get together again
soon. 11. He gave him the go-ahead to get started. He said, Go ahead, it's fine. 12.
It was such a let-down to lose in the finals. We felt that we'd let down the
whole school. 13. B goes between A and C. 14. He was a reluctant go-between for the
warring factions. 15. They wanted to try out for the team, but they missed the
tryouts. 16. Could you pick me up at five o'clock, please, and bring me a coffee as
I'll need a pick-me-up. 17. It's freezing. We need to warm up. Let's do some warm-up
exercises before we start yoga. 18. Back up. You're standing too close to the edge.
If you fall off, we'll need a backup plan. 19. I took out cash from the ATM, so let's
order takeout. 20. Darn. I mixed up millions and billions on the math test.
What a mix-up.